(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-05T22:01:42.087343",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment until the show begins
フブキ
Fubuki
ミオ
Mio
G-A-M-E-R-S
おかゆ
Okayu
ころね
Korone
Are you ready?
Go
G-A-M-E-R-S
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment until the show begins.
フブキ
Fubuki
ミオ
Mio
おかゆ
Okayu
Yeah!
ころね
Korone
G-A-M-E-R-S
おかゆ
Okayu
ころね
Korone
Yeah!
Are you ready?
Go!
Perfect!
G-A-M-E-R-S
フブキ
Fubuki
ミオ
Mio
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment for the performance to start.
G-A-M-E-R-S
ころね
Korone
Are you ready?
Go!
おかゆ
Okayu
G-A-M-E-R-S
ふぶき
Fubuki
みお
Mio
G-A-M-E-R-S
おかゆ
Okayu
ころね
Korone
Are you ready?
Perfect!
G-A-M-E-R-S
フブキ
Fubuki
ミオ
Mio
G-A-M-E-R-S
おかゆ
Okayu
ころね
Korone
No
Are you ready?
Perfect
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Okay
ミオ
Mio
G-A-M-E-R-S
Okay
ころね
Korone
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Please wait a moment until the show starts.
ホロライブ ゲーマー ズ！
Hololive Gamers!
(G-A-M-E-R-S) We are GAMERS!!!!
みんな待ってたー？
Did everyone wait for us?
いっぱい楽しい思い出作ろうねー！
Let's make lots of fun memories!
We are GAMERS!
狐じゃーい！
I'm a fox!
こーん！とキツネが登場 白髪ケモミミ 白上フブキです
Kon! A fox appears! White hair and animal ears, I'm Shirakami Fubuki!
すっ転んでちゃ始まらない 君もすこん部に入部しなさい
Falling down gets us nowhere, so join the Sukon-bu club too!
Hi friends!! (Yeah!!) Hi friends!! (Yeah!!)
古今東西 コーン茶をちょうだい
From all times and places, give me corn tea!
AIじゃないし 得意はMC
I'm not an AI, my strength is hosting!
赤い糸より 金の鯉が推し
Rather than the red thread of fate, I prefer the golden carp!
みなさん！
Everyone!
うち うち うちだよ 大神ミオだよ 黒髪ケモミミ狼 (みおーん！)
It's me, me, it's me, Ookami Mio! Black-haired animal-eared wolf (Mioon!)
本気で止めます like a ママ 笑い出すと止まらない ゲラゲラ
I'll stop you for real like a mama! Once I start laughing I can't stop, hyper-giggling!
つまり実はPONってコト！？ 小足ステップしちゃう音
Wait, does that mean I'm actually clumsy!? The sound of light-footed steps!
タロット占いで見る未来 ホラーゲームはやりたくない！
Seeing the future with tarot reading... I don't wanna play horror games!
4人揃えば ゲーマー ズ最強
When the four of us gather, Gamers are the strongest!
君も遊ぼうよ Bダッシュ
Come play with us too, B-dash!
クリア目指して レベル上げ
Leveling up to aim for a clear!
今日は何プレイしよう
What shall we play today?
君のハートも攻略しちゃう
We'll conquer your heart too!
選択をして シミュレーション
Make your choice, simulation!
初見も古参も対戦よろしく
First-timers and veterans alike, nice to play with you!
やっぱりゲームは楽しいね
Gaming really is fun, isn't it?
(G-A-M-E-R-S) We are GAMERS!!!!
(G-A-M-E-R-S)
おかゆー！
Okayu!
いっくよー もぐもぐ～ 猫又おかゆ
Here I go, mogumogu~ Nekomata Okayu!
おにぎり おにぎりは いっどうぞー
Rice balls, rice balls, here you go~
きらきら ふらふら しゃーない猫だもん
Sparkling, wandering around, can't be helped, I'm a cat after all!
ふーん そっかぁ 僕でよくない？
Hmm, I see, aren't I good enough?
まったり ゆっくり 跳ねるリズム
Laid-back and slow, a bouncing rhythm!
全肯定する おかゆイズム
Total validation, that's Okayu-ism!
全行程 効率OK
Whole process, efficiency OK!
毎日僕とい〜〜っしょ！
Together with me every single day!
ころねー！
Korone!
おぁよ〜 ゆびゆび ワンワン
Oayo~ Yubi yubi, woof woof!
パンをコネコネ 戌神ころね
Kneading bread, Inugami Korone!
犬種 キャバリア・キング・チャールズ・スパニエル
Dog breed: Cavalier King Charles Spaniel!
懐くけど 圧かける
I'm affectionate, but I put on pressure!
訛る イントネーション
Accent in my intonation!
割れる リアクション
Loud, cracking reaction!
まずは指を捧げてくれる？ 配信ショー
First, will you offer up your fingers? Stream show!
わがったなー ほーね 指示厨おけ
Got it~ Okay~ Backseat gamers welcome!
好物のはレトロゲー お届け
Delivering my favorite retro games!
4人揃えば ゲーマー ズ最高
When the four of us gather, Gamers are the best!
フラグが立てば すぐ回収
Whenever a flag is raised, immediately collect it!
エイム鍛えて 狙い撃ち
Train your aim and take the shot!
今日は何プレイしよう
What shall we play today?
君のハートを回復しちゃう
We'll restore your heart!
ワクワクするね このダンジョン
So exciting, this dungeon!
“耐久”っていうか 止められない
It's less an "endurance stream" and more that I can't stop!
だってゲームが好きなんだもん
'Cause I just love games so much!
突然ですが、ボーナスチャレンジの時間です。大きな声でレスポンスをして高得点を狙いましょう！
It's sudden, but it's time for a Bonus Challenge! Respond in a loud voice and let's aim for a high score!
Say!! こーん こんっ！ (こーん こんっ！)
Say!! Kon kon! (Kon kon!)
Say!! みおーん みおん！ (みおーん みおん！)
Say!! Mioon mion! (Mioon mion!)
Say!! もぐっ もぐっ！ (もぐっ もぐっ！)
Say!! Mogu mogu! (Mogu mogu!)
Say!! ゆびっ ゆびっ！ (ゆびっ ゆびっ！)
Say!! Yubi yubi! (Yubi yubi!)
(PERFECT！！) おぁ〜〜！！！！
(PERFECT!!) Woah~~~~!!!!
4人揃えば ゲーマー ズ最強
When the four of us gather, Gamers are the strongest!
上手く行かなくても コンティニュー
Even if it doesn't go well, continue!
全クリするまで 諦めない
Won't give up until 100% completion!
エンディングを見に行こう
Let's go watch the ending together!
君のハートも攻略しちゃう
We'll conquer your heart too!
選択をして シミュレーション
Make your choice, simulation!
初見も古参も対戦よろしく
First-timers and veterans alike, nice to play with you!
やっぱりゲームは楽しいね
Gaming really is fun, isn't it?
(G-A-M-E-R-S) We are GAMERS!!!!
こうしてさいたまスーパーアリーナに平和が訪れたのであった――
And thus, peace came to Saitama Super Arena...
はい！ということで始まりましたー！
Alright, and so it has begun!
いや、すごいね！ホロライブゲーマーズフェス 超超超超ゲーマーズ2です！
Wow, amazing! Hololive Gamers Fes Chouchouchouchou Gamers 2!
はい、じゃあちょっとね、自己紹介やっていきますかね。
Alright, let's do a quick round of introductions, shall we?
はい！皆さん！こんこんきーつね！
Hi everyone! Kon-kon kitsune!
こんこんきーつね！白上フブキです！よろしくお願いします！
Kon-kon kitsune! I'm Shirakami Fubuki! Nice to meet you!
そしてそしてね、まあ1曲目ちょっとね、あの『We are GAMERS』やらせてもらったんですけども...
And then, well, for our first song we got to perform "We are GAMERS", but...
ついにね！4人ということで！
Finally, all four of us are here!
いるじゃないですか！赤いのが！さあ！
Look, she's here! The red one! Come on!
はい！うち、うち！うちだよー！
Yes! It's me, it's me! It's me~!
おお、髪が赤い！...あ、違う！
Ooh, her hair is red! ...Ah, wait!
そうだよね！大神ミオの皆さん！
That's right! Everyone who's an Ookami Mio fan!
大神ミオの皆さん、いらっしゃいませー！
Welcome to all the Ookami Mio fans!
何だよ「大神ミオの皆さん」って！おかしいだろ！
What do you mean "Ookami Mio's fans"?! That sounds weird!
はい、続いて！はい！
Alright, next up! Here you go!
もぐもぐ〜おかゆ〜！はい、どうも！猫又おかゆで〜す！
Mogu mogu~ Okayu~! Hello everyone! I'm Nekomata Okayu!
今日はね、最高の思い出を作って、楽しんじゃいましょう！
Today, let's make the best memories and have lots of fun!
はい、そして〜！はい！
Alright, and next~! Here you go!
はい！ゆびゆび〜！ゆびゆび〜！
Yes! Yubi yubi~! Yubi yubi~!
みんな、今日は大事な日なの。何の日か知ってる？
Everyone, today is an important day. Do you know what day it is?
今日はね... 大谷翔平の誕生日ー！
Today is... Shohei Ohtani's birthday!
ということで、戌神ころねです！よろしくお願いします！
Anyway, I'm Inugami Korone! Nice to meet you!
ということで改めまして、4人揃っても、ちゅーことでね！
So once again, all four of us are together!
『ホロライブゲーマーズフェス 超超超超ゲーマーズ2』そのDay1がここ、さいたまスーパーアリーナで開幕でございます！
"Hololive Gamers Fes Chouchouchouchou Gamers 2" Day 1 is kicking off here at Saitama Super Arena!
大きい！なんとですね、あのDay1、Day2、両席とも完売ということで！
It's huge! And amazingly, both Day 1 and Day 2 are completely sold out!
すごーい！なので、Day1, Day2 ともに約1万... なんか5000とか7000とかのファンの皆さんが今日来てくださってる！
Awesome! So for both Day 1 and Day 2, around 15,000 to 17,000 fans have come out today!
そうなんです！運営さんから、Day1、Day2 合わせて約3万5千人くらいですって！
That's right! Management told us that combined Day 1 and Day 2, it's around 35,000 people!
すごーい！すごすぎる！何人いるの？！
Awesome! That's incredible! How many people is that?!
すごいね！ほぼ人間じゃん！
Amazing! Almost all of them are humans!
ほぼ人間だよ！人間以外ほぼいないだろ！
They are mostly human! There's hardly anyone here who isn't human!
1回目はね、国立代々木競技場第一体育館だったんですけども、今回はさいたまスーパーアリーナということで。
The 1st time was at Yoyogi National Gymnasium First Gymnasium, but this time we're at Saitama Super Arena.
すごいですよ、もう！ありがとうございます！
It's amazing! Thank you so much!
さて改めまして、このイベントはですね、ゲームが大好きな我々ゲーマーズを中心に、超超超超豪華な...ちょっと「超」多かったか...
Now to re-explain, this event centers around us Gamers who love games, together with super super super super grand guests... wait, did I say "super" too many times...
...ゲストと一緒に様々なゲームタイトルに挑戦したり、ライブパフォーマンスを行うプレミアムイベントです！
...challenging various game titles and delivering live performances in a premium event!
しかも今回皆さんね、あの突然出てきて「えっ3Dなの！？」って感じだったんですけど、4人でお揃いの衣装お披露目でございますー！
And what's more, today we suddenly appeared and everyone was like "Wait, it's in 3D?!", but we're showing off matching outfits for all 4 of us!
ねー！本当この衣装可愛いから着たいねって言ってたら、用意してくださいました！ありがとうございます！
Right?! We kept saying how cute these outfits are and how we wanted to wear them, and they prepared them for us! Thank you so much!
本当に可愛いですよねー！
They really are so cute!
可愛い！ありがとうございます！
So cute! Thank you very much!
さらにですね、会場では一部撮影OKのパートがありますので...
Furthermore, in the venue there are parts where taking photos is allowed...
...そちらではぜひね、スマホでお写真を撮っていただけると嬉しいです！ぜひ最後まで一緒に楽しみましょう！
...so during those times, we'd love for you to take pictures on your phones! Let's enjoy this to the end together!
ということで始まっていくんですけども、1人ずつちょっと意気込みをお願いしたいと思いますよ！
So as we get started, I'd like each of us to share our enthusiasm!
じゃあまずは、ミオから！
So first off, Mio!
はい！
Yes!
今年は、去年はね、ちょっとお休みしちゃったんですけど
This year... well, last year I had to take a break,
今年は4人でね、無事に開催することができたので
but this year all four of us were able to hold this,
明日も無事に終えられるように
so to make sure tomorrow finishes smoothly too,
体調管理だけはしっかりして、明日も過ごしたいと思います！がんばるぞー！
I'll take good care of my health and give it my all! I'll do my best!
大！大！大！頑張れ！
Dai! Dai! Dai! Do your best!
ではでは、続いては...おかゆ！
Now then, next up is... Okayu!
はーい！
Yeees!
ま、僕はね、去年引き続いての参加となるんですが
Well, I'm participating again following on from last year,
今日はね、大谷翔平の誕生日ということでね
and today happens to be Shohei Ohtani's birthday,
めでたい！おめでとう！大谷おめでとう！
Congrats! Happy birthday, Ohtani!
硬式だけどさ
Even though it's hardball...
なので、打率3割目指して頑張りたいと思います！
I want to aim for a .300 batting average and do my best!
ちょっと！低くない？！ / 3割ってすごいからね！
Wait, isn't that low?! / 30% is actually amazing!
おかゆならもっと行けそうだよね！ / いやいやいや！
If it's Okayu, she could aim higher! / No no no!
そして！
And next!
はーい！
Yeees!
今日はね、翔平に素敵なホームランをプレゼント...
Today, I want to present Shohei with a wonderful homer...
翔平に？！ホームラン届けられるように？！
To Shohei?! A home run?!
届けられるように頑張るぞ！
I'll do my best to send it to him!
翔平に届けてくれー！ / 届けます！
Send it to Shohei! / Delivering it to Shohei!
イエーイ！そしてそして！
Yay! And next, next!
はい！白上はですね、皆さん
Yes! As for Shirakami, everyone,
昨年に続きまして、なんと台本の8割が白上が読み上げるということで
following on from last year, 80% of the script is being read by Shirakami!
前半前半で喉を気遣いつつ...
Taking care of your throat in the first half...
そう、黄色だらけ...そうなんです！
Yeah, full of yellow... that's right!
かすれ始めたら「あ、頑張ってるな」と思って、いっぱいサイリウム振ってください！
If my voice starts getting raspy, think 'Ah, she's trying hard' and wave your penlights!
頑張れー！ / かわいいー！
Go for it! / So cute!
お前らの声には負けねぇから、よろしくー！
I won't lose to your voices, so let's go!
はい！そしてですね！
Yes! And also!
今日と明日行われる「超超超超ゲーマーズ2」は、ABEMA PPVで生配信してます！
Super Super Super Super Gamers 2, happening today and tomorrow, is live-streaming on ABEMA PPV!
見てるー？
Are you watching~?
見てるー！
Watching!
コメントもね、我々見えておりますよー！
We can see your comments too!
ねー、ありがとうございます！
Right, thank you so much!
こちら配信チケットは絶賛発売中です！
Streaming tickets are currently on sale!
イベントが終わっても、8月4日(月)の23:59まで何度でも見返すことができます！
Even after the event, you can rewatch it as much as you want until Mon, Aug 4, 23:59!
素晴らしい！素晴らしい！購入特典といたしましては、Day 1とDay 2で異なるシチュエーションの...
Wonderful! Wonderful! As a bonus, Day 1 and Day 2 feature different situation...
限定オリジナルボイスドラマがついてきます！
limited original voice dramas!
珍しい！
How rare!
Day 1は「秘密の事前プロデュースボイス」！
Day 1 is 'Secret Pre-Production Voice'!
秘密？これエッチなやつ？
Secret? Is this a naughty one?
いやー！違います！
Nooo! It's not!
そしてDay 2は「内緒の超ゲーマーズ打ち上げボイス」！
And Day 2 is 'Secret Super Gamers After-Party Voice'!
これエッチなやつか？
Is this a naughty one?
やめろ！
Stop it!
どちらのボイスもエッチじゃないです！聴いてください！
Neither of these voices is naughty! Please listen to them!
あとはですね、我々の直筆メッセージ入りのライブ画像もついてきますので、ぜひチェックしてください！
Also, it comes with live photos featuring our handwritten messages, so check it out!
さらに！
Furthermore!
昨年行われました「超超超超ゲーマーズ」のダイジェスト映像がABEMAプレミアムで配信中です！
a digest video of last year's 'Super Super Super Super Gamers' is streaming on ABEMA Premium!
昨年のもめちゃくちゃ面白かったので、ぜひとも見てください！
Last year's was super fun too, so please check it out!
お願いしまーす！
Please do!
さらにさらに！イベント後にグッズの受注販売が開始します！
And even more! Event merchandise pre-orders will start after the event!
ありがたいことにDay 1のグッズが完売らしくて、皆ありがとうございます！
Gratefully, Day 1 merchandise is apparently sold out! Thank you everyone!
ありがとうみんなー！
Thank you, everyone!
こちらグッズの受注販売は、本日の朝10:00から7月21日(月)の23:59まで！
Merchandise pre-orders run from 10:00 AM today until July 21st (Mon) 23:59!
Cyber Goods Storeにて受付中でございます！
Accepting orders now at Cyber Goods Store!
こちらのグッズ、9月下旬までにはお届け予定とのことです！
These goods are scheduled to be delivered by late September!
そしてなんと、事後限定グッズとしましてアクリルパネルが追加されます！
And what's more, acrylic panels are being added as post-event exclusive goods!
イベント限定グッズが手に入る最後のチャンスなので、ぜひぜひこちらチェックしてください！
It's your last chance to get these event-exclusive goods, so please check them out!
先生の話、大人しく聞けない生徒みたいになってます...
They're like students who can't quietly listen to the teacher...
見て！たぬきと犬と猫が戯れてるよ！
Look! A raccoon dog, a dog, and a cat are playing!
先生も話すからねー！
Teacher's going to talk too, okay?!
はい！さらにさらに！もうご存知の方もいらっしゃると思いますが...
Yes! And even more! Some of you might already know, but...
NTTドコモさんの「home 5G」とのコラボ実施が決定しました！
A collaboration with NTT Docomo's 'home 5G' has been decided!
イエーイ！
Yay!
先生の話を聞かなくてもいいけど、声援は出さない！
You don't have to listen to the teacher, but no cheering!
docomoさんのご紹介をしてたでしょう？！
I was introducing Docomo, wasn't I?!
どうぞー！
Go ahead!
友達か！
Are we classmates?!
え、入り口でもらえるうちわ、
The hand fans you get at the entrance,
皆さんゲットしましたかー？
did everyone get one?
もらった方ー！
Who got one?
もらったうちわも使って、
Use the hand fans you received,
熱中症対策万全にして、
take proper precautions against heatstroke,
最後まで楽しんでくださーい！
and enjoy yourselves until the very end!
熱中症対策ね、ホントに。
Seriously, keep safe from the heat.
まだまだ続きますよー！
We still have a long way to go!
超ゲマズで我々ゲーマーズを応援したいという声が多かったので、
Since many wanted to support us Gamers at Choo GAMERS,
今回イベントでCheerSPOT様とのコラボも成功いたしましたー！
we partnered with CheerSPOT for this event!
誰でも簡単に好きなチャージスポットの場所に白上たちゲーマーズの応援広告を出すことができます！
Anyone can easily display Gamers support ads at their favorite Charge Spot locations!
これすごいー！
That's so cool!
会場内もね、これなんとね、スポットが我々になっていまして、
Even inside the venue, the spots feature us,
びっくりしました。
which blew my mind.
そうなんだ！
Is that so!
見てないの！？
You haven't seen it?!
見てたよ！パネルのやつか！
I saw it! The ones on the panels, right?
そうそう！
Yeah, exactly!
ご覧になれなかった方は会場内に確かあったと思いますので、良かったら見てください。
If you missed them, they're inside the venue, so please check them out.
そしてさらに、さいたまスーパーアリーナ会場内で、
And furthermore, inside Saitama Super Arena,
等身大を初お披露目！
life-size figures are being revealed for the first time!
3月のEXPO会場で発表されました、フブミオの
Following the FubuMio figures announced at Expo in March,
等身大に続きまして、おかころのフィギュアも発売され、4人揃ってお披露目されました！
OkaKoro figures were also released, so all four are now displayed together!
事前の告知配信ではさ、無かったらおかあさんの毛玉欄じゃねぇかって言ってたんですけど、ちゃんと揃ってましたね。
In the announcement stream, we joked Okayu's might just be a furball, but they're all here!
めちゃめちゃ可愛かったですね！
They were super cute!
ありがとうございます。そしてまた本日から新作のフィギュアがデザインここから順次開始です！
Thank you. And starting today, pre-orders for new figure designs are opening sequentially!
イエーイ！可愛いー！
Yay! So cute!
イベント開催を記念して、
To celebrate the event,
8月7日までにコトブキヤで予約してくれた方には、特典のステッカーがプレゼントされるそうです！
pre-ordering at Kotobukiya by August 7th gets you a special bonus sticker!
可愛いすぎる！
Too cute!
やっぱりね、白上とミオも欲しいなーという、そう思った
And for those who were thinking, "I want Fubuki and Mio too!"
そこのあなた！あなた！あなた！
You right there! And you! And you!
なんと！
Guess what!
超ゲマズ2の開催を記念して、期間限定でフブミオ追加入荷を開始じゃー！
To celebrate Choo GAMERS 2, FubuMio pre-orders are reopened for a limited time!
逃したよーっていうのもね、何人か見かけましたので、
We saw people saying they missed out,
これを機会に是非ともご予約お願いします！
so please take this opportunity to pre-order!
そして最後に、カンダフル様による協賛企業グッズ、
And finally, sponsor goods by Candaful,
超超超超ポップコーンと、超超超超グリルチキンのご紹介でございます！
Super Super Super Super Popcorn and Super Super Super Super Grilled Chicken!
今回のイベントのキービジュアルが全面に出たデザインとなっているとのことです。
The designs feature the event's key visual across the whole package.
ポップコーンは税込1,000円で、缶詰めは税込1,500円での販売でございます。
Popcorn is ¥1,000 incl. tax, and the canned chicken is ¥1,500 incl. tax.
ポップコーンは塩キャラメル味、
Popcorn comes in salted caramel flavor,
缶詰めはグリルチキン味になってます。
and the canned chicken is grilled chicken flavor.
トレカも付いてます。
They also come with trading cards.
こちらのグッズは他のグッズと異なり、受注生産ではなく数量限定商品のため、ご注意ください！
Unlike other merch, these are limited quantity, not made-to-order, so please be careful!
集合アクリルパネルも含めて事後でしか購入できないグッズですので、
Including the group acrylic panel, these items are only available post-event,
皆さん是非確認してください！
so please make sure to check them out!
お願いしまーす！
Please do!
なんとなんと！ちなみに今回は韓国でライブビューイングもやってるそうですよ！
Also, word has it there's a live viewing in Korea!
韓国の皆さん、アンニョンハセヨ〜！
Everyone in Korea, annyeonghaseyo~!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
ではですね、色々ご紹介も終わりましたので早速！
Now that we've finished all the announcements, let's get right into it!
最初に行うゲームタイトルを発表しちゃいましょう！
Let's announce the very first game title!
行きますよー！せーの、
Here we go! Ready, set,
こちら！
This one!
ビビッター！
"Vivitter"!
こちらルールは超簡単！
The rules for this are super simple!
ミニゲームに対し、タイミングよくボタンを押してギリギリで止めるだけ！
Just hit the button at the right time in each mini-game to stop it at the very last moment!
なるほど！
I see!
我々の度胸を試す究極のビビりチェッカーゲームとなっております！
It's the ultimate chicken test game to test our courage!
よりギリギリを攻めると「Cool」の評価がもらえそうです！
Pushing it closer to the limit earns you a "Cool" rating!
今回ですね、我々個人戦でございます！
This time, we're playing as individuals!
1つのミニゲームに対して2人がそれぞれ挑戦します。
For each mini-game, two of us will challenge it.
様々な組み合わせで合計6ゲームお届けしたいと思います！
With various matchups, we'll bring you six games in total!
こちらですね、我々の「Cool」の合計数で1位を決めたいと思いますのでよろしくお願いします！
The winner will be determined by who gets the most "Cools" overall!
ではですね、ゲームを始める前に、なんと今回巨大コントローラーを用意してくれたということで、
Now, before starting the game, they've actually prepared a huge controller for us!
召喚しましょう！
Let's summon it!
それでは会場の皆さんも一緒に、「いでよ、巨大コントローラー！」と叫んでくれると嬉しいです。行きますよ！
Everyone in the venue, please shout with us, "Come forth, giant controller!" Here we go!
あー！
Ah!
おー！
Oh!
巨大コントローラーを出してもらうために...
To get the giant controller brought out...
ここに来てますからね！皆さん、行きますよー！
...we're standing right here! Everyone, here we go!
せーの！
Ready, set...
いでよ！巨大コントローラー！
Come forth! Giant controller!
きたー！
It's here!
出た出た！
It's out, it's out!
すごい！かわいいー！
Amazing! So cute!
我々のマークになっている！
It has all of our icons on it!
かわいい！
So cute!
では、どの順番でチャレンジしていきますか？
So, in what order should we take on the challenge?
我こそはという人！
Anyone who wants to go first?
えー！
Eh?
我こそは？
Anyone?
じゃあ、でもミオしゃじゃない？やっぱり。
Well, shouldn't Mio-sha go first after all?
えっ！？
Huh?!
おかえり！ミオしゃ、おかえり！
Welcome back! Welcome back, Mio-sha!
やった方がいいて！
You definitely should!
そうだよ！ミオしゃ！
That's right, Mio-sha!
1番手はミオで！
Mio will be number one!
続いてはどうする？
Who should go second?
2人目！
Second person!
やりたい？やりたい！
Do you want to go? I do!
じゃあ、おかゆ2番目。
Then Okayu second.
えぇ！？
What?!
おかゆ！おかゆ！
Okayu! Okayu!
じゃあ、おかゆ2番目！
Then Okayu second!
流れ的にね！ごめん！
Just logically, you know! Sorry!
3番目は？
What about 3rd?
どっちが3・4？
Which of you is 3 and 4?
トリは嫌だ！3番手！
I don't want to be last! 3rd!
あはは！
Ahaha!
自由なしきりだなー！
What a casual setup!
対戦としましては1番最初、ミオおかゆ！
For the match, the very first will be Mio vs Okayu!
ミオおかゆの対戦になります！
It'll be Mio versus Okayu!
1番手！
First up!
ということで、本番やっていきましょう！
So let's get into the main game!
イェーイ！
Yay!
ミオちゃんさ、僕が勝っても泣かないでね？
Mio-chan, don't cry if I win, okay?
おかゆには何度も負かされてきてるし！
I've been beaten by Okayu so many times!
この猫、めちゃくちゃミニゲーム系強いんですよ！
This cat is crazy good at mini-games!
ちょっと強いよねー。
She's pretty strong.
強すぎるまである！
She might even be too strong!
このゲーム初見だからさ。初めてやるよ！
I'm seeing this game for the first time. First time playing!
適性が高すぎんだって、ミニゲームの！
Your adaptability for mini-games is just too high!
確かにそれはあるかも。
That might actually be true.
そこでおうちが勝ったら、めっちゃ奇跡的ってことでしょ！
If I win here, it'll be a total miracle!
そんなことないよ！
That's not true!
ミオちゃんも！
Mio-chan too!
それじゃあ、やっていきますか！
Well then, shall we get started?
はーい！
Yeees!
色々ゲームがあるんですけど、まずは「試練の2」というものを...
There are various games, but first we'll do "Trial 2"...
やっていこうかなと思います！
...which we're going to try out!
今回スタッフさんがやったんですけど、スタッフさんが強すぎる！
The staff tested it this time, but they were way too good!
確かにちょっとどうにかしてる感じはするんですけど。
Indeed, it felt a bit insane.
じゃあ準備いいですか、ミオ？
Are you ready, Mio?
はーい！
Yes!
それでは行きますよ！がんばれー！
Here we go then! Do your best!
スタート！
Start!
あちらのお客様からグラスを滑らせろ！
"From the customer over there, slide the glass!"
なんか、ナンパするやつね！
It's like that picking-people-up thing!
「マスター、あちらの美しい女性に一杯」
"Master, a drink for that beautiful lady over there."
かしこまりましたー！
"Right away!"
なんだこいつの顔！
What's with his face!
クリックすると？まずは練習ですか。
If you click...? Practice first?
グラスを滑らせろ！
Slide the glass!
やってみたいと思います。
Let's try it out.
左にゲージがある。長押ししてゲージを溜めるらしく...
There's a gauge on the left. Press and hold to fill it...
ことか！
I see!
おー！
Oh!
ちょっと行き過ぎたか？
Did it go a bit too far?
えー！
Eh?!
届かなきゃいけないんでしょ！
It has to reach, right?!
それでは本番！
Now for the real thing!
行きます！
Here I go!
ここだ！
Right here!
おー！すごい！
Oh! Amazing!
COOL!
凄ーい！0.50秒！
Amazing! 0.50 seconds!
すごい！すごい！
Awesome! Awesome!
え、何そのポーズ！
Wait, what is that pose!
真ん中でやりなよ！
Do it in the center!
そっかそっか！そうよね！
Right, right! True!
でもちょっと早かった！
But that was pretty fast!
任せとけ、任せとけ！
Leave it to me, leave it to me!
ということでミオは今、50だったかな？
So Mio got 0.50 just now, right?
0.50だね！
0.50, yeah!
0.50ということで！続いてはおかゆなんですけど...
With 0.50! Next up is Okayu...
どうですか？
...how are you feeling?
いけますか？自信あり？
Can you do it? Confident?
頑張りまーす！
I'll do my best!
倒してやれ！
Beat her!
それではいきますよ！おかゆのVIVITER...
Here we go then! Okayu's Vivi Trial...
スタート！
Start!
あちらのお客様からですね！
From the customer over there!
さて、おかゆも練習があります！
Okay, Okayu gets practice too!
練習あるの優しい！
Nice that there's practice!
かしこまりましたー！
Right away!
練習お願いします！
Practice please!
練習はまずはね！
Practice first!
グラスを滑らせろ！
Slide the glass!
いけるか？
Can she do it?
あれ？
Huh?
自分の注文じゃねーかそれ！
Isn't that your own order?!
やばい！本番になっちゃった！
Oh no! It switched to the real thing!
本番だよ！頑張れ！
It's the real thing! Good luck!
ママー！
Mama!
ダメじゃないですか！
That's no good!
言ったでしょ！
I told you!
そんなお尻フリフリで...
Shaking your butt like that...
騙されないんだからねー
I'm not gonna fall for it~
ほらー
Look~
これで勝てませんかね？
Can't I win with this?
勝てるわけないだろー！
There's no way you can win with that!
ミオちゃん強かったー
Mio-chan was so strong~
難しそうだね これね
This one looks pretty tough.
いやーねー
Yeah, really.
ということで 皆さん
And with that, everyone...
こちら突然ではございますが お知らせでございます！
It's sudden, but we have an announcement!
なんと無料配信をご覧の皆様は ここまでとなります！
The free broadcast ends here for those watching!
えー！？
What?!
続きをご覧になりたい方はぜひ ABEMA PPVにて...
If you'd like to watch the rest, please head to ABEMA PPV...
チケットの購入をお願いします！
...and purchase a ticket!
お願いします！
Please do!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
ねー これからね めちゃめちゃ楽しいゲーム...
Yeah, from here on, we have super fun games...
ゲストもいるのでね！
...and special guests, too!
楽しんでいただけると思います！ よろしくお願いします！
We hope you enjoy it! Thank you so much!
それでは！
Well then!
またねー！ バイバーイ！
See you! Bye-bye!
無料パートは終了いたしました 全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
The free portion has ended. Watch the full event on ABEMA PPV!
無料パートは終了いたしました
全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
The free portion has ended.
Watch the full stream on ABEMA PPV!
G-A-M-E-R-S
フブキ！
Fubuki!
3, 2, 1, Go!
G-A-M-E-R-S
おかゆ！
Okayu!
ころね！
Korone!
ミオ！
Mio!
Are you ready?
No!
Perfect!
G-A-M-E-R-S
無料パートは終了いたしました
The free portion has ended.
全編はABEMA PPVにて視聴可能！
You can watch the full event on ABEMA PPV!